Ivy Ledbetter Lee Papers, 1881-2003 (bulk 1915-1946): Finding Aid MC085
Public Policy Papers
- Series 7: Ivy Lee and Associates, 1910-1961; 92 boxes
  - Subseries 7D: Matter Sent Out (MSO), 1914-1947; 90 boxes
    - Pennsylvania Railroad, 1920-1947; 16 boxes
      - Speeches, 1921-1934; 6 folders (Box 102, Folder 1-6)
      - Long Island Railroad Papers, 1926-1931; 1 folder (Box 102, Folder 7)
      - Long Island Railroad Papers, 1927-1944; 5 folders (Box 103, Folder 1-5)
      - Menus (West), 1924; 1926; 2 folders (Box 103, Folder 6-7)
      - Menus (West), 1927-1930; 4 folders (Box 104, Folder 1-4)
      - Menus, 1922; 1 folder (Box 104, Folder 5)
      - Printed, 1920-1925; 1 folder (Box 104, Folder 6)
      - Printed, 1926-1946; 3 folders (Box 105, Folder 1-3)
      - Ads, 1921-1935; 1 folder (Box 105, Folder 4)
      - Articles, 1921-1922; 1 folder (Box 105, Folder 5)
      - Misc. letters and statements, 1923; 1 folder (Box 105, Folder 6)
      - "Information", 1920-1929; 3 folders (Box 105, Folder 7-9)
      - "Pennsylvania Standard", 1921-1925; 1 folder (Box 106, Folder 1)
      - Airlines, 1929-1932; 1 folder (Box 106, Folder 2)
      - Legal Proceedings, 1921-1936; 1 folder (Box 106, Folder 3)
    - Perkins, George W. (Foods & Markets, New York State), 1917; 1 folder (Box 106, Folder 4)
    - The Petroleum Industries Committee, 1932; 1 folder (Box 106, Folder 5)
    - Petroleum War Service Committee, 1917-1918; 1 folder (Box 106, Folder 6)
    - Philco Corporation, 1940-1941; 2 folders (Box 106, Folder 7-8)
    - Phillipine Islands, American Chamber of Commerce of the "Phillipine Progress", 1924-1926; 1 folder (Box 106, Folder 9)
    - Prairie Pipe Line Corporation, 1932; 1 folder (Box 107, Folder 1)
    - Presbyterian Church, Layman's Committee of, 1926; 1 box
      - 1926, 1 folder (Box 107, Folder 2)
      - News Bulletins, 1926; 1 folder (Box 107, Folder 3)
    - Presbyterian Church USA, 1925; 1 folder (Box 107, Folder 4)
    - Poland, 1927-1930; 1 box
      - (Bankers Trust Loans), 1927; 1 folder (Box 107, Folder 5)
      - 1928-1930, 2 folders (Box 107, Folder 6-7)
      - Printed, 1928-1929; 1 folder (Box 107, Folder 8)
      - "Bulletin of the Bank of Poland", 1928-1929; 2 folders (Box 107, Folder 9-10)
    - Princeton University, 1919-1941; 2 boxes
      - Endowment Fund, 1919-1920; 1 folder (Box 107, Folder 11)
      - Endowment Fund, Printed, 1919-1921; 1 folder (Box 108, Folder 1)
      - Miscellaneous, 1921-1922; 1 folder (Box 108, Folder 2)
      - News Releases, 1925-1926; 1 folder (Box 108, Folder 3)
      - Printed, 1923-1926; 1 folder (Box 108, Folder 4)
      - (Daily Princetonian Alumni Association), 1937-1941; 1 folder (Box 108, Folder 5)
    - Public Utility Executives, Committee of, 1935-1936; 2 boxes
      - 1935 February-April, 5 folders (Box 108, Folder 6-10)
      - 1935-1936, 6 folders (Box 109, Folder 1-6)
    - Realty Stabilization Company, 1933; 1 folder (Box 109, Folder 7)
    - Republican National Committee, 1917; 1 folder (Box 109, Folder 8)
    - Riverside Church, 1929-1946; 2 boxes
      - 1929-1943, 1 folder (Box 109, Folder 9)
      - Printed, 1929-1934; 1 folder (Box 110, Folder 1)
      - Printed, 1946; 1 folder (Box 110, Folder 2)
    - Rockefeller Interests, 1914-1946; 4 boxes
      - General Education Board, 1914-1931; 4 folders (Box 110, Folder 3-6)
      - International House, 1932; 1937-1938; 1 folder (Box 110, Folder 7)
      - Laura Spelman Rockefeller Memorial, 1922-1923; 1 folder (Box 110, Folder 8)
      - Rockefeller Center, 1935-1938; 1 folder (Box 110, Folder 9)
      - John D. Rockefeller Jr, 1917-1923; 1 folder (Box 110, Folder 10)
      - John D. Rockefeller Jr, 1925-1946; 5 folders (Box 111, Folder 1-5)
      - John D. Rockefeller Sr, 1918-1937; 1 folder (Box 111, Folder 6)
      - Rockefeller family, 1922-1946; 2 folders (Box 111, Folder 7-8)
      - Rockefeller Foundation, 1915-1918; 3 folders (Box 111, Folder 9-11)
      - Rockefeller Foundation, 1919-1920; 2 folders (Box 112, Folder 1-2)
      - Rockefeller Institute for Medical Research, 1915-1920; 1927-1939; 2 folders (Box 112, Folder 3-4)
      - Williamsburg, 1928-1944; 1 folder (Box 112, Folder 5)
      - Miscellaneous- Printed, undated; 1 folder (Box 112, Folder 6)
      - Bureau of Social Hygiene, Printed, 1917; 1 folder (Box 112, Folder 7)
      - Printed material by John D. Rockefeller Jr, 1915-1945; 2 folders (Box 112, Folder 8-9)
      - Printed material on John D. Rockefeller Jr, 1928; 1 folder (Box 112, Folder 10)
      - Rockefeller Foundations, Printed, 1915-1916; 1 folder (Box 112, Folder 11)
      - Rockefeller Foundations, Printed "Newsletter" #1-6, 1916-1919; 1 folder (Box 112, Folder 12)
      - Rockefeller Institute for Medical Research, Printed, 1916; 1919; 1 folder (Box 113, Folder 1)
    - Rotary Club of New York, 1938-1939; 1 folder (Box 113, Folder 2)
    - Rumania, 1928-1929; 1 folder (Box 113, Folder 3)
    - St. Bartholomew's Church, 1930-1931; 1 folder (Box 113, Folder 4)
    - Schiff, Mortimer L, 1919; 1921; 1 folder (Box 113, Folder 5)
    - Seaman's Church Institute, 1925-1926; 1 folder (Box 113, Folder 6)
    - Society for the Propagation of Faith, 1943 March; 1 folder (Box 113, Folder 7)
    - Socony-Vacuum Oil Company, Inc., 1935-1946; 2 boxes
      - 1935-1944, 5 folders (Box 113, Folder 8-12)
      - 1945-1946, 2 folders (Box 114, Folder 1-2)
      - Printed, 1936-1946; 3 folders (Box 114, Folder 3-5)
    - Southwestern Gas and Electric Company, 1923; 1 folder (Box 114, Folder 6)
    - Speyer & Company, 1924-1925; 1 folder (Box 114, Folder 7)
    - Standard Cap & Seal Corporation, 1943 July-December; 1 folder (Box 114, Folder 8)
    - Standard Oil Company, 1917-1931; 2 boxes
      - 1917- 1920, 1 folder (Box 114, Folder 9)
      - A.C. Bedford, Chairman, speeches, 1922; 1 folder (Box 114, Folder 10)
      - Proxy fight, 1928-1929; 1 folder (Box 114, Folder 11)
      - 1931, 1 folder (Box 115, Folder 1)
    - Standard Soapstone, 1925; 1 folder (Box 115, Folder 2)
    - Steamship Conference, 1925; 1 folder (Box 115, Folder 3)
    - Steinmetz, Charles P. (Electric Transportation), 1923; 1 folder (Box 115, Folder 4)
    - Stevenson, Charles, 1932; 1 folder (Box 115, Folder 5)
    - Strong, Sturgis & Company, 1916-1919; 1 folder (Box 115, Folder 6)
    - Steuben Society of America, 1927; 1 folder (Box 115, Folder 7)
    - Stuyvesant Square Thrift Shop, 1938-1944; 1 folder (Box 115, Folder 8)
    - Sugar Interests, 1922-1946; 1 box
      - Czarnikow-Rionda Company, "The Sugar Newsletter", 1922; 1 folder (Box 115, Folder 9)
      - American Producers of Cuban Sugar, 1922-1923; 1 box
        - 1922-1923, 1 folder (Box 115, Folder 10)
        - Bulletins 1-12, 1922 January-August; 1 folder (Box 115, Folder 11)
      - American Sugar Refining Company, 1946; 1 folder (Box 115, Folder 12)
      - miscellaneous, 1930-1931; 1 folder (Box 115, Folder 13)
      - International Sugar Council, 1932; 1934; 1 folder (Box 115, Folder 14)
      - United States Cuban Sugar Council, 1946; 1 folder (Box 115, Folder 15)
    - Taylor-Wharton Iron and Steel Company, 1941-1943; 2 folders (Box 115, Folder 16-17)
    - Taunton-New Bedford Copper Company, 1922; 1 folder (Box 115, Folder 18)
    - Teachers College, Columbia University, 1919- 1920; 1 folder (Box 115, Folder 19)
    - Thompson, Dorothy, 1939; 1 folder (Box 115, Folder 20)
    - Thompson- Starrett Company, 1927-1930; 1 box
      - 1927-1930, 1 folder (Box 115, Folder 21)
      - "The Skyscraper", 1928- 1930; 1 folder (Box 115, Folder 22)
    - Tidewater Assoc. Oil Company, 1936; 1 folder (Box 115, Folder 23)
    - Title Guarantee & Trust Company, 1933; 1 folder (Box 115, Folder 24)
    - Town Hall (New York City), 1924; 1 folder (Box 116, Folder 1)
    - Traylor, Melvin A. (Presidential Candidate), 1932; 1 folder (Box 116, Folder 2)
    - Trenton and Mercer County Traction Company, 1919; 1 folder (Box 116, Folder 3)
    - United China Relief, 1942; 1 folder (Box 116, Folder 4)
    - Union Pacific System, 1919; 1 folder (Box 116, Folder 5)
    - United Artists, 1924; 1 folder (Box 116, Folder 6)
    - United Club Residence Inc., 1927-1928; 1 box
      - (Barbizon Hotel), 1927-1928; 1 folder (Box 116, Folder 7)
      - Printed, 1927-1928; 1 folder (Box 116, Folder 8)
    - United Gas and Electric Company, 1916-1917; 1 folder (Box 116, Folder 9)
    - United Hospital Fund, 1916-1925; 2 folders (Box 116, Folder 10-11)
    - United States Army Engineers District, 1944; 1 folder (Box 116, Folder 12)
    - United States Distribution Corporation, 1920; 1924; 1925; 1 folder (Box 116, Folder 13)
    - United States-France Financial News Corporation, 1921; 1 folder (Box 116, Folder 14)
    - United States Revolver Association, 1922-1923; 1 box
      - 1922-1923, 1 folder (Box 116, Folder 15)
      - "Bulletins", 1923; 1 folder (Box 116, Folder 16)
    - United States Rubber Company, 1919-1923; 1 box
      - 1919-1921, 1 folder (Box 116, Folder 17)
      - 1923, 1 folder (Box 116, Folder 18)
    - University of Virginia, 1936-1945; 2 boxes
      - 1936-1938, 1 folder (Box 116, Folder 19)
      - 1944, 1 folder (Box 116, Folder 20)
      - Printed, 1944 April-November; 1 folder (Box 117, Folder 1)
      - Alumni Fund, Printed, 1943-1945; 1 folder (Box 117, Folder 2)
    - Vacuum Oil Company, 1930; 1 folder (Box 117, Folder 3)
    - Waldorf-Astoria Hotel, 1930-1931; 1 box
      - 1930- 1931, 1 folder (Box 117, Folder 4)
      - Printed, 1930-1931; 1 folder (Box 117, Folder 5)
    - Washburn Crosby Company, 1923-1926; 1 folder (Box 117, Folder 6)
    - Westchester Title and Trust, 1933; 1 folder (Box 117, Folder 7)
    - Western Union Telegraph Company, 1918-1946; 2 boxes
      - 1939-1946, 4 folders (Box 117, Folder 8-11)
      - 1946, 1 folder (Box 118, Folder 1)
      - Printed, 1918; 1 folder (Box 118, Folder 2)
      - Printed, 1941- 1946; 2 folders (Box 118, Folder 3-4)
    - West End Chemical Company (Borax), 1921; 1 folder (Box 118, Folder 5)
    - Whist Club, 1944; 1 folder (Box 118, Folder 6)
    - Wickwire Spencer Steel Company, 1941-1946; 1 box
      - 1941-1942, 2 folders (Box 118, Folder 7-8)
      - Ads, 1942; 1 folder (Box 118, Folder 9)
      - Printed, 1943-1946; 1 folder (Box 118, Folder 10)
    - William A. Sunday Evangelistic Association, New York, 1917; 1 folder (Box 118, Folder 11)
    - Woman's Roosevelt Memorial Association, 1919-1921; 1 folder (Box 118, Folder 12)
    - Woodworth, N. A. Company, 1943 July; 1 folder (Box 118, Folder 13)
    - Wynkoop Service (Insurance Experts), 1919; 1 folder (Box 118, Folder 14)
    - York Railways Company, 1918-1919; 1 folder (Box 118, Folder 15)
    - Young Men's Christian Association, 1925-1937; 1 box
      - Bowery branch, 1935-1937; 1 folder (Box 118, Folder 16)
      - Student World Court, 1925-1926; 1 folder (Box 118, Folder 17)
    - Young Women's Christian Association, War Work Council, 1918; 1 folder (Box 118, Folder 18)
- Series 8: Oversize Materials, 1898-1946; 18 boxes
  The oversize series contains a variety of items illustrating Ivy Lee's career. Included are news articles written by Lee while he was a journalist, his obituaries, and a scrapbook of memorabilia from Ivy Lee's work with the American Red Cross. The material for Ivy Lee and Associates consists of memorandum and reprints of various articles and speeches of interest to Lee. Material includes the U. S. Chamber of Commerce and recognition of the Soviet Union, disarmament debates in House of Commons 1931, "Business Opinion and Banking Policy," The "Gold Clause," and "Sources of International News. Also included are editions of Public Affairs and Public Relations from 1924. Box 123 contains a complete run of Information from 1924 to 1933. This publication of Ivy Lee & Associates is an excellent source of information on issues of concern and the thoughts of Lee. Many of Lee's clients are highlighted in the issues.
  This series also includes oversize Matter Sent Out material. Companies with only one or two items are in the miscellaneous folders. The material consists of advertisements, reprints of newspaper editorials, press releases, posters, and informational sheets for the public. Please check the folder listing for a complete list of the companies with oversized material. Companies with a large quantity of material have been put in separate boxes. Included are a complete run of the Association of Railroad Executives Railroad Data. This was sent to member railroads with information to use in their public relations efforts. The Interborough Rapid Transit Company published the Subway Sun and Elevated Express. The files contain a complete run of these posters. The posters were displayed in subway cars giving the public information on route changes, places of interest to see, general information, and pleas for an increase in the subway fares. Only one copy of either publication has been saved since they were exact duplicates of each other.
  The Pennsylvania News was issued by region to the employees of the Pennsylvania Railroad. The paper contained information on the railroad, material on employees such as their years of service with the railroad or sports teams sponsored by the railroad, and also material aimed at wives and children. Due to its deteriorating condition many of the Pennsylvania News issues were not saved. The Copper and Brass Research Institute issued a number of large posters and advertisements which are included in this series. The Committee of Public Utility Executives issued many information sheets to illustrate their point of view to the public.
  - Oversize - smaller, 1898-1934; 5 boxes
    - Articles by Ivy Lee, 1898-1903; 1 box (Box 119)
    - Obituaries, 1934; 1 box (Box 120)
    - Memorabilia, Red Cross Scrapbook, 1917-1918; 1 box (Box 121)
    - Ivy Lee and Associates, 1924-1933; 2 boxes
      - Miscellaneous printed, undated; 1 folder (Box 122, Folder 1)
      - "Public Relations," and "Public Affairs", 1924; 1 folder (Box 122, Folder 2)
      - "Information", 1924-1933; 1 box (Box 123)
  - Oversize - smaller, Matter Sent Out, 1917-1945; 8 boxes
    - American Classical League, 1924-1925; 1 folder (Box 124, Folder 1)
    - American Red Cross, 1917; 1 folder (Box 124, Folder 2)
    - American Ship and Commerce Corporation, 1920; 1 folder (Box 124, Folder 3)
    - American Tobacco Company, 1929; 1931-1933; 1 folder (Box 124, Folder 4)
    - Armour Incorporated, 1923-1924; 1 folder (Box 124, Folder 5)
    - "Bakelite Information", 1927-1928; 1 folder (Box 124, Folder 6)
    - Bethlehem Steel, 1917; 1921-1926; 1 folder (Box 124, Folder 7)
    - Cement Manufacturers Association, 1922-1923; 1 folder (Box 124, Folder 8)
    - Corning Glass Works, 1945; 1 folder (Box 124, Folder 9)
    - Harvard Law School, 1925; 1 folder (Box 124, Folder 10)
    - Institute of Public Administration, 1936; 1 folder (Box 124, Folder 11)
    - International Chamber of Commerce, 1921-1922; 1 folder (Box 124, Folder 12)
    - Layman's Foreign Missions Inquiry, 1931-1933; 1 folder (Box 124, Folder 13)
    - Logan County Operators Association "The Miners Lamp", 1921; 1 folder (Box 124, Folder 14)
    - Marineland Studios, 1938; 1 folder (Box 124, Folder 15)
    - Montreal Light, Heat and Power Company, 1925; 1 folder (Box 124, Folder 16)
    - National Board of Fire Underwriters, 1943; 1945; 1 folder (Box 124, Folder 17)
    - Philippine American Chamber of Commerce, 1925; 1 folder (Box 124, Folder 18)
    - Princeton University, 1919; 1925; 1 folder (Box 124, Folder 19)
    - Socony-Vacuum Oil Company, 1930; 1937; 1 folder (Box 124, Folder 20)
    - Whist Club, 1932; 1 folder (Box 124, Folder 21)
    - Association of Railroad Executives, 1919-1932; 2 boxes
      - "Railway Data" and "American Railroads", 1919-1924; 1 box (Box 125)
      - "Railroad Data", 1925-1932; 1 box (Box 126)
    - Interborough Rapid Transit, "IRT News", 1927-1931; 1 box (Box 127)
    - Pennsylvania Railroad, 1923-1932; 4 boxes
      - "Pennsylvania New," Central and Altoona Works, 1929-1932; 1 box (Box 128)
      - "Pennsylvania News," Eastern Region, 1929-1932; 1 box (Box 129)
      - "Pennsylvania News," Northwestern and Southerwestern Regions, 1924; 1923-1925; 1 box (Box 130)
      - "Pennsylvania News," Western Region, 1929-1931; 1 box (Box 131)
  - Oversize - large, Matter Sent Out, 1918-1946; 5 boxes
    - Miscellaneous A-Z, 1919-1945; 1 folder (Box 132, Folder 1)
    - American Petroleum Institute, 1918-1923; 1 folder (Box 132, Folder 2)
    - Anthracite Operators, 1922-1926; 1 folder (Box 132, Folder 3)
    - Association of Railroad Executives, 1920-1921; 1 folder (Box 132, Folder 4)
    - Bankers Trust Company, 1920; 1 folder (Box 132, Folder 5)
    - Briggs Manufacturing Company, 1942-1943; 1 folder (Box 132, Folder 6)
    - Chrysler Corporation, 1932-1941; 1 folder (Box 132, Folder 7)
    - Cotton Interests, 1926-1930; 1 folder (Box 132, Folder 8)
    - Cuban Sugar Interests, 1923-1946; 1 folder (Box 132, Folder 9)
    - Eastern Presidents Conference, 1923; 1 folder (Box 132, Folder 10)
    - Georgia Railroad and Power Company, 1921-1922; 1 folder (Box 132, Folder 11)
    - Guggenheim Interests, 1925-1929; 1 folder (Box 133, Folder 1)
    - Harvard University, 1924; 1 folder (Box 133, Folder 2)
    - Kahn, Otto H, 1918-1924; 1 folder (Box 133, Folder 3)
    - League of Nations Information Service, 1924; 1 folder (Box 133, Folder 4)
    - Licensed Beverage Industries, 1946; 1 folder (Box 133, Folder 5)
    - New York Railways Company, 1918-1919; 1 folder (Box 133, Folder 6)
    - New York Trust, "The Index", 1932; 1 folder (Box 133, Folder 7)
    - Pennsylvania Railroad, 1920-1942; 1 folder (Box 133, Folder 8)
    - Rockefeller Interests, 1920-1946; 1 folder (Box 133, Folder 9)
    - Stueben Society of America, 1923; 1 folder (Box 133, Folder 10)
    - Traylor, Melvin A, 1932; 1 folder (Box 133, Folder 11)
    - Copper and Brass Research Institute, 1922-1931; 1 box (Box 134)
    - IRT "Subway Sun" and "Elevated Express", 1926-1932; 1 box (Box 138)
    - Public Utility Executives, Committee on, 1935-1936; 1 box (Box 139)
- Series 9: Visual Materials, 1881-1971; 14 boxes; 1 folder
  The photographs include Ivy Lee, Lee family members, photos of Germany taken by James W. Lee II, Matter Sent Out photos, and Lee's large collection of autographed photographs that graced his office walls. The photos of Lee span the years of 1881 to 1932. Many of the photos are undated but appear to be taken during the 1920s. There are also four photographs Lee took while at Emory University and photos taken at the ceremonies of Ivy Lee Day in Cedartown, Georgia in 1965. The family photographs contain members of the immediate family and one portrait of a Lee family gathering that includes Lee's brothers and sisters. Also included is a folder of photographs taken on the family trip "Seeing America" in the summer of 1926. The German photos taken by James W. Lee II in 1933 and 19434 are of Nazi rallies that were enclosed in letters to his parents.
  During World War II, Ivy Lee & Assoc. sent photos out with the MSO material. Only selected photographs have been saved since most were exact duplicates. The photos generally highlight the war work being done by various clients. Many of the photos feature women on the assembly line and in other areas of work. The Marine Studios photos are publicity pictures of the building of the world's largest aquarium at the time, including pictures of the marine life that inhabited the new tourist attraction in Florida. There are 6 boxes of autographed photographs, arranged alphabetically, once hung on Ivy Lee's office walls.
  The visual materials series includes a newsreel of Ivy Lee titled This Man Speaks for the Great: Ivy Lee Relates an intimate anecdote for a noted client, John D. Rockefeller, Sr. There is also footage of Ivy Lee, Jr. in an interview with Allen Center discussing Ivy Lee, Sr. recorded in the Spring of 1971.
  Arranged by type of materials.
  - Photographs, 1881-1965 October; 2 boxes
    - Ivy Lee small photographs, 1881-1932; 1 folder (Box 140, Folder 1)
    - Ivy Lee medium photographs, undated; 1 folder (Box 140, Folder 2)
    - Photographs taken by Lee while at Emory University, 1895; 1 folder (Box 140, Folder 3)
    - Ivy Lee Day, Cedartown, Georgia photographs, 1965 October; 1 folder (Box 140, Folder 4)
    - Lee family small photographs, undated; 1 folder (Box 141, Folder 1)
    - Lee family medium photographs, undated; 1 folder (Box 141, Folder 2)
    - Lee family Seeing America trip photographs, 1928; 1 folder (Box 141, Folder 3)
    - Lee, James W. II, German photographs, 1933-1934; 1 folder (Box 141, Folder 4)
  - Matter Sent Out Photographs, 1937-1945; 1 box
    - Briggs Manufacturing Company, 1942-1945; 1 folder (Box 142, Folder 1)
    - Chrysler Corporation, 1942-1943; 1 folder (Box 142, Folder 2)
    - Marineland Studies, 1937-1938; 1 folder (Box 142, Folder 3)
    - N. A. Woodworth Company, 1942; 1 folder (Box 142, Folder 4)
    - National Diary Products, undated; 1 folder (Box 142, Folder 5)
    - Rotary Club, undated; 1 folder (Box 142, Folder 6)
  - Autographed photographs, dates not examined; 6 boxes
    - Ivy Lee large photographs, undated; 1 folder (Box 143, Folder 1)
    - Office inventories of autographed photographs, undated; 1 folder (Box 143, Folder 2)
    - Agassiz, R. L., dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 143, Folder 3)
    - Armsby, George, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 143)
    - Armsby, George, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 143)
    - Atterbury, W. W., dates not examined; 1 box (Box 143)
    - Aylesworth, Merlyne H., dates not examined; 1 box (Box 143)
    - Baker, George Barr, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 143)
    - Bell, James F., dates not examined; 1 box (Box 143)
    - Benes, Dr. Edward, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 143)
    - Benn, Sir Ernest, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 143)
    - Berlin, Irving, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 143)
    - Berwind, Ernest J., dates not examined; 1 box (Box 143)
    - Brisbane, Arthur, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 143)
    - Biekel, Karl A., dates not examined; 1 box (Box 143)
    - Bliss, Cornelius N., dates not examined; 1 box (Box 143)
    - Boomer, Lucius, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 143)
    - Brash, Matthew C., dates not examined; 1 box (Box 143)
    - Breed, William C., dates not examined; 1 box (Box 143)
    - Brown, Dr. Elmer E., dates not examined; 1 box (Box 143)
    - Brown, James, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 143)
    - Bryd, Admiral Richard, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 143)
    - Buck, Gene?, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 143)
    - Budd, Ralph, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 143)
    - Bullock, Professor Charles J., dates not examined; 1 box (Box 143)
    - Cadman, S. Parkes, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 143)
    - Chadbourne, Thomas L., dates not examined; 1 box (Box 143)
    - Chrysler, Walter P., dates not examined; 1 box (Box 143)
    - Churchill, Winston, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 144)
    - Ciechanowski, Jan ?, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 144)
    - Clement, M. W., dates not examined; 1 box (Box 144)
    - Cleveland, Grover, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 144)
    - Cohen, John S., dates not examined; 1 box (Box 144)
    - Compton, Karl T., dates not examined; 1 box (Box 144)
    - Coolidge, Calvin, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 144)
    - Coy, Harvey W., dates not examined; 1 box (Box 144)
    - Cravath, Paul D., dates not examined; 1 box (Box 144)
    - Crowther, Samuel, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 144)
    - Curtis, Cyrus H. K., dates not examined; 1 box (Box 144)
    - Cuyler, Thomas D., dates not examined; 1 box (Box 144)
    - Davis, Donald D., dates not examined; 1 box (Box 144)
    - Davis, J. M., dates not examined; 1 box (Box 144)
    - Davis, J. W., dates not examined; 1 box (Box 144)
    - Davison, F. Trubee, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 144)